{
    "id": "5d6b121b96914eeab8ebcc4db68c3930",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Speak",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0ae0ea0601ea40a7bba5b4b5acba8a24",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs With Speak",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "When I said work hours should be reduced I was speaking ............................. all employees.",
                    "description": "To speak for is to speak on somebody's behalf.",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The restaurant gets really crowded in the evenings. Be sure to speak ................................... a table.",
                    "description": "To speak for a table is to reserve it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is a fabulous writer. Her stories speak ................................... themselves.",
                    "description": "When a story speaks for itself, it represents a certain quality.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am speaking ................................ myself, not for my colleagues.",
                    "description": "To speak for yourself is to speak on your behalf.",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This act speaks .................................... his generosity.",
                    "description": "Speak of can mean indicate or suggest.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You should learn to speak ................................. your opinion.",
                    "description": "To speak out your opinion is to assert it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "off",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Her songs really speak ................................. me.",
                    "description": "If something speaks to you, it resonates with you.",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please speak .................................. I can't hear you properly.",
                    "description": "To speak up is to talk more loudly.",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "up",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "No one speaks ..................................... for the oppressed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "to",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I found his behavior unacceptable but I didn’t dare to speak ……………………….. about it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "If this happens again, you have to speak ………………………… him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "to",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Last few months have been very dry – no rain to speak …………………………..",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "of",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}